Inventory to the Annelise Graebner Anderson Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Office of Management and Budget, 1981-1983 (Box 28-139)
  - Money Supply/Credit Market Report (Box-folder 76: 25)
  - Balances of Budget Authority – Budget for Fiscal Year 1982 (Box-folder 76: 26)
  - Congressional Quarterly Weekly Report – January 17, 1981 (Box-folder 76: 27)
  - Overall Estimated for Budget (Box-folder 76: 28)
  - Federal Government Budget Data (Box-folder 77: 1)
  - Meeting with the Congressional Black Caucus Concerning the President’s Economic Program (Box-folder 77: 2)
  - Fact Sheet – Accelerated Cost Recovery System (Box-folder 77: 3)
  - President Reagan’s Economic Program (Box-folder 77: 4)
  - Economic and Financial Update (Box-folder 77: 5)
  - Regaining a Stable Price Level by Arthur F. Burns (Box-folder 77: 6)
  - Consumer Opinion Survey – A Chamber/Gallup Survey (Box-folder 77: 7)
  - Impact of Budget Cuts on New Jersey (Box-folder 77: 8)
  - Fact Sheet – Interim Report on Savings and New Initiatives Resulting From OMB Bulletin NO. 81-16 (Box-folder 77: 9)
  - Alice Rivlin’s Testimony Before the House Budget Committee (Box-folder 77: 10)
  - Newspaper Articles (Box-folder 77: 11)
  - Memorandums (Box-folder 77: 12)
  - Economic Report – November 1981 (Box-folder 77: 13)
  - President’s Address (Box-folder 77: 14)
  - Budget Savings and Tax Reductions (Box-folder 77: 15)
  - Budget Fact Sheets – April 2, 1981 (Box-folder 77: 16)
  - The Federal Budget for 1983 (Box-folder 77: 17)
  - Status Report on Reductions Proposed in the March 1981 Budget Revisions (Box-folder 77: 18)
  - The Reagan Budget: Still Too Timid – February 18, 1982 (Box-folder 77: 19)
  - Preliminary CBO Estimates of the Mid-Session Review – August 26, 1981 (Box-folder 77: 20)
  - Talking Points (Box-folder 77: 21)
  - Interview With David Stockman, Director of Office Of Management And Budget – March 9, 1981 (Box-folder 77: 22)
  - Transportation Speech – May 1, 1981 (Box-folder 77: 23)
  - 1981 Appropriations for FRA – April 22, 1981 (Box-folder 77: 24)
  - Housing Programs – Department of Housing and Urban Development – April 14, 1981 (Box-folder 77: 25)
  - Talking Points on Gonzalez II – December 14, 1982 (Box-folder 77: 26)
  - Veterans Benefits and Services/Administration of Justice/General Government/Interest/Allowances (Box-folder 77: 27)
  - Concurrent Resolution (Box-folder 77: 28)
  - Talking Points Opposing Congressman Reuss’s Proposed Program for Economic Recovery/Coast Guard Funding (Box-folder 77: 29)
  - Expenditure Reductions (Box-folder 77: 30)
  - Economic and financial Update – April 11, 1981 (Box-folder 77: 31)
  - Regional Tables – Annual Data (1980-1986) (Box-folder 77: 32)
  - Economic Comparison Of Reagan and Carter Programs, by State and by Region (Box-folder 77: 33)
  - Major Cuts Proposals (Box-folder 77: 34)
  - House Budget Committee: Markup of Budget Resolution – April 7, 1981 (Box-folder 77: 35)
  - CUED (Box-folder 77: 36)
  - Remarks of Annelise Anderson – May 5, 1981 (Box-folder 77: 37)
  - Revised Fact Sheet on the Bipartisan Tax Reduction Program (Box-folder 78: 1)
  - Map and Directions for Parking in Rosslyn/Talking Points/Economic and Financial Update (Box-folder 78: 2)
  - Relocation of Fort Chaffee Population/Talking Points – July 13, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 3)
  - Draft Memo and Draft Talking Points for Director’s Meeting – April 9, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 4)
  - Talking Points on Tourism Legislation – May 28, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 5)
  - Talking Points for Ed Harper – February 1, 1982 (Box-folder 78: 6)
  - Talking Points for Joseph Wright – April 30, 1982 (Box-folder 78: 7)
  - War Risk Insurance Bill, H.R. 5930 Talking Points – “Alleghany-Mohawk Provisions” (Box-folder 78: 8)
  - Talking Points from Legislative Affairs – August 4, 1982 (Box-folder 78: 9)
  - Talking Points on Legalization Provisions (Box-folder 78: 10)
  - Talking Points Opposing H.R. 6100, The National Development Investment Act (Box-folder 78: 11)
  - Talking Points for Community Renewal Act (CRA) – August 6, 1982 (Box-folder 78: 12)
  - Talking Points – August 8, 1982 (Box-folder 78: 13)
  - Reductions in FY 1982 (Box-folder 78: 14)
  - Reagan Projections Minus Carter Projections (Box-folder 78: 15-16)
  - Issue Outline for the “Federal Loans and Guarantee” – April 24, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 17)
  - Economic Assumptions (Box-folder 78: 18)
  - Heritage Foundation Study – March 12-April 8, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 19)
  - Econ pkg. documents (Box-folder 78: 20)
  - Post on “Clearing Up the Confusion” – March 13, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 21)
  - The Classical Economic Case for Cutting Marginal Income Tax Rates (Box-folder 78: 22)
  - Report to the President and Cabinet – July 13, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 23)
  - “The Minimum Wage: Restricting Jobs for Youth” – July 1, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 24)
  - Economic and Financial Update – May 2, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 25)
  - Economic and Financial Update – June 27, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 26)
  - Talking Points – Democratic Tax Plan – June 26, 1981 (Box-folder 78: 27)
  - Supplemental Veto Override in the House – September 10, 1982 (Box-folder 78: 28)
  - Draft Proposal for Policy Implementation Review – April 27, 1982 (Box-folder 78: 29)
  - Final Edition of the 1981 House of Representatives Voting Analysis – April 8, 1982 (Box-folder 78: 30)
  - Weekly Activities Report (Box-folder 78: 31-32)
  - Department of Transportation – United States Coast Guard (Box-folder 79: 1)
  - A Summary Report of Inspectors General Activities – FY 1981 II (Box-folder 79: 2)
  - Commerce (Box-folder 79: 3)
  - HUD 1982 (Box-folder 79: 4)
  - General Revenue Sharing CDBG (Box-folder 79: 5)
  - Treasury 1982 (Box-folder 79: 6)
  - Transportation (Box-folder 79: 7)
  - Politics (Box-folder 79: 8)
  - 1982 Budget 3rd Resolution (Box-folder 79: 9)
  - Local Content (Box-folder 79: 10)
  - Auto Industry (Box-folder 79: 11)
  - Asbestos (Box-folder 79: 12)
  - Appropriations (Box-folder 79: 13)
  - Legislative Problems (Box-folder 79: 14-15)
  - Legislative Problems (Box-folder 80: 1)
  - Amtrak (Box-folder 80: 2-3)
  - Amtrak Federal Debt Relief (Box-folder 80: 4)
  - Final House Budget Committee Action on the First Budget Resolution for 1983 Round II – June 4, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 5)
  - Tables in Conjunction With DAS’s Negotiations on the Budget Resolution – June 7, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 6)
  - Worksheet Summary of Policy Changes Agreed Upon By the House Republicans – June 8, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 7)
  - Tables Prepared for DAS’s Use in Discussion With the House Republican Caucus – June 3, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 8)
  - Credit Tables – June 9, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 9)
  - Latta-II Function Summary (Box-folder 80: 10)
  - Materials on Latta Bipartisan Compromise and Jones Democratic Leadership Proposal (Box-folder 80: 11)
  - Continuing Resolution (Box-folder 80: 12)
  - Bridge From CBO Base to Senate-Passed (in millions of dollars) (Box-folder 80: 13)
  - Conference Worksheet: S. Con. Res. 92 – Budget Aggregates (Box-folder 80: 14)
  - Legislative Affairs Miscellaneous Notes (Box-folder 80: 15)
  - Reconciliation – by Senate Committee (Box-folder 80: 16)
  - Briefing Materials for the Director – August 9, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 17)
  - Section 108 Loan Guarantees (Box-folder 80: 18)
  - First Budget Resolution For FY 1983 (Box-folder 80: 19)
  - Tables Comparing the House and Senate Reconciliation Instructions (Box-folder 80: 20)
  - CBO tables distributed at the conference on the Budget Resolution – June 17, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 21)
  - Tables Comparing Function Totals for 1982 – May 27, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 22)
  - Preliminary Revenue Increase Options – June 2, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 23)
  - Copies of the Senate Budget Resolution Summary Tables – June 2 (Box-folder 80: 24)
  - Summary Tables Relating to the First Senate Budget Resolution + Copy of Resolution (Box-folder 80: 25)
  - Preliminary Information sent to Jim Baker in Versailles – June 4, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 26)
  - Talking Points – House Budget Failure – May 28, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 27)
  - House Budget Committee Mark-Up on the First Concurrent Budget Resolution for 1983 – Round II (Box-folder 80: 28)
  - Questionable Credit Budget Savings Under the Gramm Balanced Budget Substitute – June 3, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 29)
  - Functional Bridge Tables for the Bipartisan Alternative (Box-folder 80: 30)
  - Tables Relating to Latta Function (Box-folder 80: 31)
  - Congressional Back-up Tables – May 10, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 32)
  - House Budget Resolution/Budget Amendments (Box-folder 81: 1)
  - Copies of Arguments for Housing and Transportation (Box-folder 81: 2)
  - Preliminary Tables Assessing the Conference Passed Budget Resolution (Box-folder 81: 3)
  - Five Revised Decision Papers – Illegal Immigration (Box-folder 81: 4)
  - Immigration and Refugees Notes (Box-folder 81: 5)
  - Justice/INS Legislation (Box-folder 81: 6)
  - Articles on Immigration (Box-folder 81: 7)
  - Testimony of William French Smith Attorney General – July 30, 1981 (Box-folder 81: 8)
  - Legislative Referral Memorandum (Box-folder 81: 9)
  - Amendments (Box-folder 81: 10)
  - Notes on Latta, COLA, Postal Service Funding (Box-folder 81: 11)
  - Immigration – Active File (Box-folder 81: 12)
  - AG Meeting (Box-folder 81: 13)
  - Krome North/Frank Hodsell/Immigration (Box-folder 81: 14)
  - Budget Strategy for Immigration Task Force Policy (Box-folder 81: 15)
  - Immigration Issues (Box-folder 81: 16)
  - Labor’s Testimony on Payment of Unemployment Taxes by Employers of Alien Farm Workers – October 29, 1981 (Box-folder 81: 17)
  - Talking Points on the Issue of Customs Taking on Drug Investigative Work (Box-folder 81: 18)
  - Immigration Emergency Legislation (Box-folder 81: 19)
  - Immigration (Box-folder 82: 1-3)
  - Fort Chaffee Notes (Box-folder 82: 4)
  - Immigration Reform Bills (Box-folder 82: 5)
  - Draft Report of the President’s Task Force on Immigration and Refugee Policy (Box-folder 82: 6)
  - Reconciliation 83 Budget (Box-folder 82: 7)
  - Conference on Budget Resolution/Status of Conference Discussions/Tables (Box-folder 82: 8)
  - CBMS Products – June 30, 1982 (Box-folder 82: 9)
  - Senate Activity/Entitlements (Box-folder 82: 10)
  - Senate Budget Committee Backup (Box-folder 82: 11)
  - First Budget Resolution for FY 1983 – June 14, 1982 (Box-folder 82: 12)
  - Copy of the final worksheet for the first 1983 budget resolution (Box-folder 82: 13)
  - Immigration and Refugees (Box-folder 82: 14-15)
  - Immigration and Refugees (Box-folder 83: 1)
  - Immigration (Box-folder 83: 2-3)
  - Immigration – Cabinet (Box-folder 83: 4-5)
  - Administration/Small Business Administration/Talking Points (Box-folder 83: 6)
  - Newspaper Articles – NYT (Box-folder 83: 7)
  - Health and Human Resources (Box-folder 83: 8)
  - HOLD – Balanced Budget Memo to Ed Gray (Box-folder 83: 9)
  - S.J. Res. 58 (Box-folder 83: 10)
  - News Summary for The Attorney General – December 9, 1982 (Box-folder 83: 11)
  - President’s Task Force on Immigration and Refugee Policy (Box-folder 83: 12)
  - Constraining Federal Taxing and Spending – October 21-23, 1981 (Box-folder 84: 1)
  - Public Attitudes Toward Economic Rights – A Chamber/Gallup Survey (Box-folder 84: 2)
  - The Wall Street Journal articles – November 3, 1981 and February 4, 1982 (Box-folder 84: 3)
  - The National Tax Limitation Committee (Box-folder 84: 4)
  - A New Monetary Constitution? – An Evaluation of the Need and the Major Alternatives (Box-folder 84: 5)
  - The Tax Revolt by Alvin Rabushka – October 21-23, 1981 - and By Lewis Uhler (Box-folder 84: 6)
  - Tax Specification and Tax Limitation by James M. Buchanan and Geoffrey Brennan (Box-folder 84: 7)
  - Has Constitutional Expenditure Limitation Become Outmoded? By Aaron Wildavsky (Box-folder 84: 8)
  - A Defense of Current Federal Budgetary Procedures by Robert W. Hartman and Robert D. Reischauer (Box-folder 84: 9)
  - Preliminary Draft by Richard Rahn – October 16, 1981 (Box-folder 84: 10)
  - Balanced Budgets and Beyond (Box-folder 84: 11)
  - Commentary on “Defense of Current Federal Budgetary Procedures” by Carol Cox (Box-folder 84: 12)
  - “Public-Sector Budgets as External Diseconomies” by Peter Aranson (Box-folder 84: 13)
  - “Controlling the Budget by Statute: An Imperfect but Workable Process” by Allen Schick (Box-folder 84: 14)
  - Comments on J.M. Buchanan and Geoffrey Brennan “Tax Specification and Tax Limits” (Box-folder 84: 15)
  - “Professionalized Service and Disabling Help” by John McKnight (Box-folder 84: 16)
  - The Balanced Budget Constitutional Amendment Talking Points Vol. II, No. 9 – July 15, 1982 (Box-folder 84: 17)
  - Articles for N.Y. Times (Box-folder 84: 18)
  - History of Congressional Votes on Major Defense Spending Bills During Urgent Military Situations (1937-1982) (Box-folder 84: 19)
  - Revised Amendments – July 30, 1982 (Box-folder 84: 20)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs – March 12, 1982 (Box-folder 84: 21)
  - Balanced Budget/Tax Limitation Talking Points first draft (Box-folder 84: 22)
  - Analysis of Inside O.M.B.’s Amendment “Flaws” – May 1982 (Box-folder 84: 23)
  - Constitutional Balanced Budget Tax Limitation Amendment (Revised Draft) – March 17, 1982 (Box-folder 84: 24)
  - Answers to Questions on Balanced Budget Following DAS Testimony – July 13, 1982 (Box-folder 84: 25)
  - Fact Sheet – Balanced Budget Amendment (Box-folder 84: 26)
  - Congressional Testimony (Box-folder 84: 27)
  - Consultative Session on the Constitutional Convention and the Budget-Balancing Amendment (Box-folder 84: 28)
  - The Balanced Budget/Tax Limitation Amendment (Box-folder 84: 29)
  - Conforming Nomenclature (Box-folder 84: 30)
  - Truly Historic Occasion – Constitutional Amendment (Box-folder 84: 31)
  - Catalogue of recorded votes taken in the Senate on S.J. Res. 58 (Box-folder 84: 32)
  - Progressive Balanced Budget System of 1981 (Box-folder 84: 33)
  - The proposed Omnibus Immigration Control Act (Box-folder 84: 34)
  - Mexico Visit – May 4, 1981 (Box-folder 84: 35)
  - The 1980 Mariel Exodus: An Assessment and Prospect (Box-folder 85: 1)
  - A Formula Solution, from: Congressional Spending (Box-folder 85: 2)
  - Contribution to the Stockman testimony from Alvin Rabushka (Box-folder 85: 3)
  - Hearing Testimony Followup Balanced Budget (Box-folder 85: 4)
  - Balanced Budget Amendment Maxi-Briefings – July 14, 1982 (Box-folder 85: 5)
  - Status of Balanced Budget Amendment on Senate Floor – July 13, 1982 (Box-folder 85: 6)
  - List of amendments offered by Senator Domenici (Box-folder 85: 7)
  - Remarks of the President at the Kickoff Rally for the Balanced Budget Amendment – July 19, 1982 (Box-folder 85: 8)
  - Data Resources Incorporated Simulation (Box-folder 85: 9)
  - Balanced Budget – Position Statements (Box-folder 85: 10)
  - Balanced Budget/Tax Limitation Amendment-Stockman Testimony – May 17, 1982 (Box-folder 85: 11)
  - Private Employment and Transfer Recipients (Box-folder 85: 12)
  - Radio Address by the President to the Nation – May 1, 1982 (Box-folder 85: 13)
  - Remarks of David A. Stockman (Box-folder 85: 14)
  - First Draft of the Director’s testimony on the balanced budget/tax limitation amendment (Box-folder 85: 15)
  - Presentation of the Honorable David A. Stockman, Director, office of management and budget before the house committee on the budget – May 5, 1982 (Box-folder 85: 16)
  - Floor Statement on Amendments to S.J. Res. 58 Balanced Budget Constitutional Amendment – July 27, 1982 (Box-folder 85: 17)
  - Statement of Senator Orrin G. Hatch of Utah (Box-folder 85: 18)
  - Amendment to S.J. Res. 58 (Box-folder 85: 19)
  - Balanced Budget Amendment Notes (Box-folder 85: 20-21)
  - Balanced Budget Amendment Notes (Box-folder 86: 22-23)
  - BBTL Amendment – Veto Power (Box-folder 86: 24)
  - Newspaper Articles (Box-folder 86: 25)
  - The Growth of U.S. Public Spending: Another Look – Thomas E. Borcherding (Box-folder 86: 26)
  - Questions and answers regarding the balanced budgets (Box-folder 86: 27)
  - Information File Originals – BBTL (Box-folder 86: 28)
  - BBTL – Sept. 82 (Box-folder 86: 29)
  - H.J. Res. 350 and S.J. Res. 58 (unamended) notes (Box-folder 86: 30)
  - Q’s and A’s – Fiscal Analysis Branch (Box-folder 86: 31)
  - Responses to Rodino Questions (Box-folder 86: 32)
  - Question from Director Stockman’s Testimony – May 19, 1982 (Box-folder 86: 33)
  - Congressional Record-Senate – August 4, 1982 (Box-folder 86: 34)
  - Discharge Petition on Balanced Budget (Box-folder 86: 35)
  - Congressman McClory’s request for mock balanced budgets for the next four years (Box-folder 86: 36)
  - Memo and Background Papers for Martin Feldstein on BBTL (Box-folder 86: 37)
  - BBTL – Report of the Committee on the Judiciary United States Senate on S.J. Res. 58/Aspects of SJR 58/HJR 350 (Box-folder 87: 1)
  - Text of a letter from the President to representatives Barber Conable and Ed Jenkins (Box-folder 87: 2)
  - Highway User Fees and Federalism (Box-folder 87: 3-4)
  - Federal-Aid Highways Obligation Limitation of $8,750,000,000 for Fiscal Year 1981 (Box-folder 87: 5)
  - FAA (Box-folder 87: 6-8)
  - DOT Legislative Proposal for Pay and Benefits to FAA Employees (Box-folder 87: 9)
  - DOT’s Draft Bill on Air Traffic Controllers (Box-folder 87: 10)
  - Commuter Aircraft Corporation (Box-folder 87: 11)
  - FAA/PATCO (Box-folder 87: 12)
  - FAA/PATCO (Box-folder 88: 1-2)
  - U.S. Research and Development (Box-folder 88: 3)
  - USTR Trade Proposals (Box-folder 88: 4)
  - Regulatory Policy and International Trade (Box-folder 88: 5)
  - Notes from USTR Mid-Term Review (Box-folder 88: 6)
  - High Technology (Box-folder 88: 7-9)
  - Agenda for Meeting with Secretary Baldrige – November 5, 1982 (Box-folder 88: 10)
  - Specialty Steel (Box-folder 88: 11)
  - Secretary Baldrige’s Presentation to the President (Box-folder 88: 12)
  - Government Financial Institutions in Support of U.S. Exports by Roger E. Shields and R. Craig Sonksen (Box-folder 88: 13)
  - 1983 Initiatives (Box-folder 88: 14)
  - Cooperative Export Finance Corporation Key Issue Review (Box-folder 88: 15)
  - CCCT Meeting of DISC Alternatives (Box-folder 88: 16)
  - Export Administration Act Renewal (Box-folder 88: 17)
  - Trade Policy/Trade Strategy (Box-folder 89: 1-2)
  - CCCT Working Group on Brock Bailout Package (Box-folder 89: 3)
  - Newspaper Articles – NYT/Washington Post (Box-folder 89: 4)
  - The Status of the Nation’s Highways: Conditions and Performance (Box-folder 89: 5)
  - Meeting with Secretary Baldrige (Box-folder 89: 6)
  - Bie Products and Clients (Box-folder 89: 7)
  - Industrial Technology Partnerships (Box-folder 89: 8)
  - Farm Sector Update (Box-folder 89: 9)
  - Cabinet Meeting: December 17 at noon (120 minutes) (Box-folder 89: 10)
  - Export Finance (Box-folder 89: 11)
  - Cabinet Council on Commerce and Trade (Box-folder 89: 12-13)
  - The Party’s Over: An Analysis of Alternative Financial and Regulatory Policies for Public Transportation in an Era without Federal Operating Subsidies (Box-folder 89: 14)
  - Tim Wirth Paper – September 20, 1982 (Box-folder 89: 15)
  - EX-IM Bank (Box-folder 89: 16)
  - DAS Testimony – House Banking, Urban Affairs – March 5, 1981 (Box-folder 90: 1)
  - EXIM Bank Briefing Book (Box-folder 90: 2)
  - Department of Transportation Issues (Box-folder 90: 3)
  - Direct Lending (Box-folder 90: 4)
  - Various Program Reductions (376, 306) (Box-folder 90: 5)
  - Section 8 Tax-exempt financing (Box-folder 90: 6)
  - White House News Summary Special Edition Vol. 1, Issue 8, April 3, 1981 (Box-folder 90: 7)
  - PRB Meeting-Briefing Book – August 7, 1982 (Box-folder 90: 8-9)
  - Final Predictions for 1982 Elections and Talking Points – October 31, 1982 (Box-folder 90: 10)
  - Letters with New York Officials (Box-folder 90: 11)
  - The Uniform Relocation Assistance Act of 1970 (Box-folder 90: 12)
  - Maritime Policy (Box-folder 91: 1-2)
  - Coast Guard Roles and Missions Study-Policy Committee Meeting – July 20, 1981 (Box-folder 91: 3)
  - Coast Guard (Box-folder 91: 4-5)
  - Post Office, National Consumer Coop Bank – February 1981 (Box-folder 91: 6)
  - General Proposals (Box-folder 91: 7)
  - Completed (Box-folder 91: 8)
  - Economic Assumptions for the Reagan Review (Box-folder 91: 9)
  - Discussion Paper – Administratively Uncontrolled Overtime (AUO) (Box-folder 91: 10)
  - Briefing Material for the President – October 17, 1981 (Box-folder 91: 11)
  - Commerce C (Box-folder 91: 12)
  - Early 1981 Action – General Memos (Box-folder 91: 13)
  - 1982 Appropriations etc. (Box-folder 92: 1)
  - Justification (Box-folder 92: 2)
  - 1982 Supp. + Rescission Bill (Box-folder 92: 3-4)
  - Transportation for discussion (Box-folder 92: 5)
  - Federal Railroad Administration (FRA) (Box-folder 92: 6)
  - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) (Box-folder 92: 7)
  - Northeast Corridor Improvement Project (NECIP) (Box-folder 92: 8)
  - Cooperative Automative Research Program (CARP) (Box-folder 92: 9)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) (Box-folder 92: 10)
  - Budget Working Group Session – February 25, 1981 (Box-folder 92: 11)
  - Department of Justice-Department of the Treasury – FY 1982 Budget Revisions (Box-folder 92: 12)
  - Spring Review: Failing Industries (Box-folder 92: 13)
  - Spring Review: Failing Industries (Box-folder 93: 1)
  - Budget Working Group Session – February 24, 1981 (Box-folder 93: 2-4)
  - 1984 Spring Review Bailout Proposals (Box-folder 93: 5)
  - Talking Points-Senate Budget Committee Package vs. Jones Package (Box-folder 93: 6)
  - More thoughts on the testimony (Box-folder 93: 7)
  - Deficit Baseline: Changes Since February Budget (in billions of dollars) (Box-folder 93: 8)
  - Discretionary Freeze at 1982 budget authority levels (Box-folder 93: 9)
  - Background Paper on FY 82 Deficit Estimate (Box-folder 93: 10)
  - Budget Negotiation Worksheets (Box-folder 93: 11)
  - Committee on the Budget U.S. House of Representatives – Reagan’s FY 1983 Budget (Box-folder 93: 12)
  - Congressional Testimony – February 23, 1982 (Box-folder 93: 13)
  - Monetary Policy Adjustments (Box-folder 93: 14)
  - House Budget Committee Mark-up (Box-folder 93: 15)
  - Latta Amendment Notes (Box-folder 93: 16)
  - Updated summary table and updated “set of 8” package on the Coalition proposals (Box-folder 93: 17)
  - CBO Reestimates of the Administration’s Current Budget Estimates, April 1982 (Box-folder 93: 18)
  - Central Budget Analysis Initiative (Box-folder 93: 19)
  - Amendments to House Budget Resolution Substitutes (Box-folder 93: 20)
  - Copy of the Domenici plan (Box-folder 93: 21)
  - Final House Budget Committee Action on the First Budget Resolution for 1983 (Box-folder 93: 22)
  - Jones (HBC) Bridge Tables, by function (Box-folder 93: 23)
  - Treasury, Postal Service, and General Government (Box-folder 94: 1)
  - Special Provisions in the Second 1983 Continuing Resolution (Box-folder 94: 2)
  - Outline and Impact of Budget Compromise Options (Box-folder 94: 3)
  - General (Box-folder 94: 4-5)
  - D.C. Government (Box-folder 94: 6)
  - Coast Guard Funding (Box-folder 94: 7)
  - Legislative Affairs memorandum cover pages (Box-folder 94: 8)
  - First Budget Resolution (Box-folder 94: 9)
  - Phone Numbers to Reach J.L. and Don today (Box-folder 94: 10)
  - DOT 1984 Fall Director’s Review (Box-folder 94: 11)
  - IRS (Box-folder 94: 12)
  - 1983 Spring Budget Overview (Box-folder 94: 13)
  - HUD and Independent Agencies (Box-folder 94: 14)
  - Military Construction Appro. (Box-folder 95: 1)
  - Status report on letters and tables for congressional action on 1983 appropriation bills (Box-folder 95: 2)
  - Transportation (Box-folder 95: 3)
  - 1984 HUD Budget Appeals (Box-folder 95: 4)
  - Issues (Box-folder 95: 5)
  - 1984 Spring Planning Review-TCH (Box-folder 95: 6-7)
  - DOC/SBA 1984 Fall Director’s Review (Box-folder 95: 8)